일어나라 그대여 aespa!
さあ 立ち上がって
Wake up!
더 치명적인 전쟁 속에
破滅的な戦いの中
In a deadlier war
두발로 버텨 적의 hook!
踏ん張って耐えて 敵のHook!
Hold on with your feet Hook!
Black Mamba
두렵지 않아 네가 hoot!
怖くない 君がHoot!
I am not afraid of you Hoot!
부셔줄게
ぶち壊してあげる
I’ll break you
달라졌어 우리가 aespa!
変わったのよ 私たちが
It has changed
>광야를 넘어 돌아올 때
KWANGYAを超えて帰ってくる時
when we entered KWANGYA
>일그러져 버렸던 æ
歪んでしまった æ
Distorted æ
>더 나답게 마치 하나처럼 보일
さらに私らしく まるでシンクロして見える
more like me, like one
>미친 존재감의 현신
ハンパない存在感の現身
A crazy presence that shows
>다시 남겨진 불씨가
取り残された火種が
The ember that was left behind
>거대한 악으로 자라나서
巨大な悪に成長して
grew into a great evil
>무기력하게 널 고립시켜 둘 때
君から気力を奪い孤立させた時
When I helplessly isolate you
>Reunite 우린 다시 함께
Reunite もう一度 一緒に
Reunite we’re together again
Whoo Whoo
덮쳐 Beat it Yah
襲い掛かれ Beat it Yah
Attack Beat it Yah
넌 혼자가 아니야
君は一人じゃない
You’re not alone
빛났던 sacrifice
輝いていた Sacrifice
Shined sacrifice
기억 찾았다면
記憶を取り戻したなら
If you found the memory
보여줄래? 나타나줄래?
姿を見せて　出てきて
Can you show us? Can you show up?
지금 여기
今すぐ ここに
Right now, right here
따라와 (Bow down)
ついて来て(Bow down)
Follow me (Bow down)
지켜봐 (My skill)
見守ってて(My skill)
Watch me (My skill)
놀랄걸 (Say wow)
驚くはず(Say wow)
You will get surprised (Say wow)
We coming
소리쳐 (Get loud)
叫んで(Get loud)
Scream (Get loud)
들어봐 (My sound)
聞いてみて(My sound)
Listen (My sound)
불러봐 (Upgrade)
呼んでみて(Upgrade)
Call it (Upgrade)
We coming
혼돈 속에서 피어나 aespa!
混沌の中で蘇る
Blooming in chaos
두려움에 맞설 그런 용기
恐怖に立ち向かう勇気
And confronting fear, That courage
(Ah Yeah)
언제라도 우린 Together Together!<>/MY
いつだって私たちは Together
Whenever we are together
We Them Girls We Them Girls
We Them Girls
Meta Universe 공존해
Meta Universe 共存する
Meta universe exists
지금 parallel world
今 Parallel World
now Parallel world
모든 존재가 의미를 가져
すべての存在が意味をもつ
All beings have meaning
Part of my heart
우린 공감의 언어를 써
私たちは共感の言語を使う
We use sympathetic words
체온을 나눠 줘
体温を分かち合い
and share the body temperatures
결국 선한 의지만의 가치를
結局善良な意志に基づく価値を
In the end, we only pursue
추구해
ひたすら追い求める
the value of goodwill
강해졌어 드디어 난 aespa!
私はついに強くなれた
I finally became stronger
휘둘리거나 당하지 않아 aespa!
振り回されたり やられたりしない
I don’t get swindled or hurt
왜곡이 돼버려 또 다
また何もかもが捻じ曲げられてしまう
It’s distorted
시작됐어 편을 갈라
始まった 仲を引き裂いて
It has started again Make sides
너와 날 고립시켜 앞 못 보게
君と私を断絶させる 何も見えないように
Isolate you and me so that we can’t see ahead
못된 욕망에 일그러져
醜い欲望に歪んでしまった
The algorithms that have been
버리던 algorithm들이
捨てたAlgorithmたちが
distorted by bad desires
존재를 무기로 파괴로
存在を武器に破壊へと
Use existence as the weapon
집어삼켜 Ah
飲み込んでしまう Ah
and swallow with destruction Ah
그 순간 악은 시작됐어
その瞬間 悪は始まった
Evil was started at that moment
Whoo Whoo
비켜 Flip Yah
どいて Flip Yah
Move out flip Yah
난 혼자가 아니야
私は一人じゃない
I’m not alone
지켜주고 싶어
守ってあげたい
I want to protect
처음 만난 네 REKALL
初めて逢う 君のREKALL
first encountering REKALL
안아줄게 느낄 수 있게
ハグしてあげる気持ちが伝わるように
I will hug you so that you can feel
Without SYNK DIVE
따라와 (Bow down)
ついて来て(Bow down)
Follow me (Bow down)
지켜봐 (My skill)
見守ってて(My skill)
Watch me (My skill)
놀랄걸 (Say wow)
驚くはず(Say wow)
You will get surprised (Say wow)
We coming
소리쳐 (Get loud)
叫んで(Get loud)
Scream (Get loud)
들어봐 (My sound)
聞いてみて(My sound)
Listen (My sound)
불러봐 (Upgrade)
呼んでみて(Upgrade)
Call it (Upgrade)
We coming
혼돈 속에서 피어나 aespa!
混沌の中で蘇る
Blooming in chaos
두려움에 맞설 그런 용기
恐怖に立ち向かう勇気
And confronting fear, That courage
(Ah Yeah)
언제라도 우린 Together Together!
いつだって私たちは Together
Whenever we are Together
We Them Girls We Them Girls
평화로운 날을 맞이해
平和な日を迎える
To face a peaceful day
우린 FLAT 그 안에서
私たちは FLAT その中で
Inside the FLAT
함께 웃고 사랑해
一緒に笑って恋をする
We laugh and love together
With my friends aespa!
이제 더 nævis와 함께
これからnævisと共に
Now I’m more curious about
열어 갈 미래가 궁금해
切り拓いていく未来が気になる
the future together with nævis
결국 만나게 될 걸
いずれ逢えるよ
Eventually we will probably meet
nævis on the REAL MY WORLD
KARINA! GISELLE! WINTER! NINGNING!
MY! aespa!
Hold up!
KARINA! GISELLE! WINTER! NINGNING!
REAL MY WORLD
넌 거울에 비친 나
君は鏡に映った私
Your existence is brighter
그보다 빛날 존재
それよりも光る存在
than my reflection in the mirror
말해 줄래?
言ってくれる？
Can you tell me?
언제까지나 함께란 걸
いつまでも一緒だよと
Until when, will we be together?
따라와 (Bow down)
ついて来て(Bow down)
Follow me (Bow down)
지켜봐 (My skill)
見守ってて(My skill)
Watch me (My skill)
놀랄걸 (Say wow)
驚くはず(Say wow)
You will get surprised (Say wow)
We coming
소리쳐 (Get loud)
叫んで(Get loud)
Scream (Get loud)
들어봐 (My sound)
聞いてみて(My sound)
Listen (My sound)
불러봐 (Upgrade)
呼んでみて(Upgrade)
Call it (Upgrade)
We coming
혼돈 속에서 피어나 aespa!
混沌の中で蘇る
Blooming in chaos
두려움에 맞설 그런 용기
恐怖に立ち向かう勇気
And confronting fear, That courage
(Ah Yeah)
언제라도 우린 Together Together!
いつだって私たちは Together
Whenever we are together
We Them Girls We Them Girls
We Them Girls
Girls!